[
	{
		"question": "爱",
		"pinyin": "ài",
		"optionA": "love; affection; be fond of",
		"optionB": "to let down",
		"optionC": "excuse me",
		"optionD": "if you please",
		"answer": "love; affection; be fond of"
	},

	{
		"question": "八",
		"pinyin": "bā",
		"optionA": "I'm Sorry!",
		"optionB": "excuse me",
		"optionC": "unworthy",
		"optionD": "eight (Kangxi radical 12)",
		"answer": "eight (Kangxi radical 12)"
	},

	{
		"question": "爸爸",
		"pinyin": "bà ba",
		"optionA": "to read",
		"optionB": "William Shakespeare",
		"optionC": "(informal) father; Dad",
		"optionD": "Dan Brown",
		"answer": "(informal) father; Dad"
	},

	{
		"question": "杯子",
		"pinyin": "bēi zi",
		"optionA": "school",
		"optionB": "A Computer",
		"optionC": "A pair of shoes",
		"optionD": "cup; glass",
		"answer": "cup; glass"
	},

	{
		"question": "北京",
		"pinyin": "Běi jīng",
		"optionA": "Beijing (capital of China)",
		"optionB": "Elephant",
		"optionC": "Goat",
		"optionD": "Lion",
		"answer": "Beijing (capital of China)"
	},

	{
		"question": "本",
		"pinyin": "běn",
		"optionA": "doctor",
		"optionB": "(mw for books); roots or stems of plants; origin; this",
		"optionC": "Sherlock Holmes",
		"optionD": "Samuel L. Jackson",
		"answer": "(mw for books); roots or stems of plants; origin; this"
	},

	{
		"question": "不",
		"pinyin": "bù",
		"optionA": "China",
		"optionB": "Blue",
		"optionC": "no; not",
		"optionD": "to study",
		"answer": "no; not"
	},

	{
		"question": "不客气",
		"pinyin": "bù kè qi",
		"optionA": "you're welcome; don't be polite; impolite",
		"optionB": "ear",
		"optionC": "legs",
		"optionD": "hands",
		"answer": "you're welcome; don't be polite; impolite"
	},

	{
		"question": "菜",
		"pinyin": "cài",
		"optionA": "play",
		"optionB": "10",
		"optionC": "to study",
		"optionD": "dish (type of food); vegetables",
		"answer": "dish (type of food); vegetables"
	},

	{
		"question": "茶",
		"pinyin": "chá",
		"optionA": "tea",
		"optionB": "Horse racing",
		"optionC": "Street Racing",
		"optionD": "Arm Wrestling",
		"answer": "tea"
	},

	{
		"question": "吃",
		"pinyin": "chī",
		"optionA": "music",
		"optionB": "Sir Isaac Newton",
		"optionC": "eat",
		"optionD": "Albert Einstein",
		"answer": "eat"
	},

	{
		"question": "出租车",
		"pinyin": "chū zū chē",
		"optionA": "taxi; cab",
		"optionB": "The Dictionary",
		"optionC": "The Bible",
		"optionD": "The Chemistry text Book",
		"answer": "taxi; cab"
	},

	{
		"question": "打电话",
		"pinyin": "dǎ diàn huà",
		"optionA": "go to work",
		"optionB": "make a phone call",
		"optionC": "Abuja",
		"optionD": "Syndey",
		"answer": "make a phone call"
	},

	{
		"question": "大",
		"pinyin": "dà",
		"optionA": "pen",
		"optionB": "to read",
		"optionC": "to interpret",
		"optionD": "big; large (Kangxi radical 37); person of importance",
		"answer": "big; large (Kangxi radical 37); person of importance"
	},

	{
		"question": "的",
		"pinyin": "de",
		"optionA": "(possessive, modifying, or descriptive particle); bull's eye; in reality",
		"optionB": "Barack Obama",
		"optionC": "Wole Soyinka",
		"optionD": "Thomas Edison",
		"answer": "(possessive, modifying, or descriptive particle); bull's eye; in reality"
	},

	{
		"question": "点",
		"pinyin": "diǎn",
		"optionA": "to learn",
		"optionB": "to decipher",
		"optionC": "a dot; a point; a bit; a little; o'clock",
		"optionD": "At that time",
		"answer": "a dot; a point; a bit; a little; o'clock"
	},

	{
		"question": "电脑",
		"pinyin": "diàn nǎo",
		"optionA": "television; TV",
		"optionB": "movie; film",
		"optionC": "computer",
		"optionD": "eat",
		"answer": "computer"
	},

	{
		"question": "电视",
		"pinyin": "diàn shì",
		"optionA": "tea",
		"optionB": "television; TV",
		"optionC": "computer",
		"optionD": "eat",
		"answer": "television; TV"
	},

	{
		"question": "电影",
		"pinyin": "diàn yǐng",
		"optionA": "tea",
		"optionB": "television; TV",
		"optionC": "computer",
		"optionD": "movie; film",
		"answer": "movie; film"
	},

	{
		"question": "东西",
		"pinyin": "dōng xi",
		"optionA": "thing; objects; stuff; (-xī: east and west)",
		"optionB": "television; TV",
		"optionC": "computer",
		"optionD": "eat",
		"answer": "thing; objects; stuff; (-xī: east and west)"
	},

	{
		"question": "都",
		"pinyin": "dōu",
		"optionA": "thing; objects; stuff; (-xī: east and west)",
		"optionB": "all; both (if two things are involved) | capital; metropolis",
		"optionC": "computer",
		"optionD": "eat",
		"answer": "all; both (if two things are involved) | capital; metropolis"
	},

	{
		"question": "读",
		"pinyin": "dú",
		"optionA": "to read; to study",
		"optionB": "sorry",
		"optionC": "computer",
		"optionD": "eat",
		"answer": "to read; to study"
	},

	{
		"question": "对不起",
		"pinyin": "duì bu qǐ",
		"optionA": "to read; to study",
		"optionB": "sorry",
		"optionC": "computer",
		"optionD": "eat",
		"answer": "sorry"
	},

	{
		"question": "多",
		"pinyin": "duō",
		"optionA": "to read; to study",
		"optionB": "sorry",
		"optionC": "many; much; a lot of; more than",
		"optionD": "eat",
		"answer": "many; much; a lot of; more than"
	},

	{
		"question": "多少",
		"pinyin": "duō shao",
		"optionA": "to read; to study",
		"optionB": "how much; how many; which (number)",
		"optionC": "many; much; a lot of; more than",
		"optionD": "eat",
		"answer": "how much; how many; which (number)"
	},

	{
		"question": "儿子",
		"pinyin": "ér zi",
		"optionA": "to read; to study",
		"optionB": "how much; how many; which (number)",
		"optionC": "many; much; a lot of; more than",
		"optionD": "son",
		"answer": "son"
	},

	{
		"question": "二",
		"pinyin": "èr",
		"optionA": "to read; to study",
		"optionB": "two (Kangxi radical 7)",
		"optionC": "many; much; a lot of; more than",
		"optionD": "son",
		"answer": "two (Kangxi radical 7)"
	},

	{
		"question": "饭店",
		"pinyin": "fàn diàn",
		"optionA": "to read; to study",
		"optionB": "two (Kangxi radical 7)",
		"optionC": "restaurant; hotel",
		"optionD": "son",
		"answer": "restaurant; hotel"
	},

	{
		"question": "飞机",
		"pinyin": "fēi jī",
		"optionA": "aeroplane",
		"optionB": "two (Kangxi radical 7)",
		"optionC": "restaurant; hotel",
		"optionD": "son",
		"answer": "aeroplane"
	},

	{
		"question": "分钟",
		"pinyin": "fēn zhōng",
		"optionA": "aeroplane",
		"optionB": "two (Kangxi radical 7)",
		"optionC": "restaurant; hotel",
		"optionD": "minute; (mw for time)",
		"answer": "minute; (mw for time)"
	},

	{
		"question": "高兴",
		"pinyin": "gāo xìng",
		"optionA": "aeroplane",
		"optionB": "happy; glad; willing (do something)",
		"optionC": "restaurant; hotel",
		"optionD": "minute; (mw for time)",
		"answer": "happy; glad; willing (do something)"
	},

	{
		"question": "个",
		"pinyin": "gè",
		"optionA": "general measure word",
		"optionB": "happy; glad; willing (do something)",
		"optionC": "restaurant; hotel",
		"optionD": "minute; (mw for time)",
		"answer": "general measure word"
	},

	{
		"question": "工作",
		"pinyin": "gōng zuò",
		"optionA": "general measure word",
		"optionB": "happy; glad; willing (do something)",
		"optionC": "restaurant; hotel",
		"optionD": "work; a job",
		"answer": "work; a job"
	},

	{
		"question": "狗",
		"pinyin": "gǒu",
		"optionA": "general measure word",
		"optionB": "dog",
		"optionC": "restaurant; hotel",
		"optionD": "work; a job",
		"answer": "dog"
	},

	{
		"question": "汉语",
		"pinyin": "Hàn yǔ",
		"optionA": "general measure word",
		"optionB": "dog",
		"optionC": "Chinese language",
		"optionD": "work; a job",
		"answer": "Chinese language"
	},

	{
		"question": "好",
		"pinyin": "hǎo",
		"optionA": "general measure word",
		"optionB": "dog",
		"optionC": "Chinese language",
		"optionD": "good; well; nice; very; quite",
		"answer": "good; well; nice; very; quite"
	},

	{
		"question": "号",
		"pinyin": "hào",
		"optionA": "number; day of a month; (mw for ordinal numbers)",
		"optionB": "dog",
		"optionC": "Chinese language",
		"optionD": "good; well; nice; very; quite",
		"answer": "number; day of a month; (mw for ordinal numbers)"
	},

	{
		"question": "喝",
		"pinyin": "hē",
		"optionA": "number; day of a month; (mw for ordinal numbers)",
		"optionB": "to drink; interjection expressing surprise",
		"optionC": "Chinese language",
		"optionD": "good; well; nice; very; quite",
		"answer": "to drink; interjection expressing surprise"
	},

	{
		"question": "和",
		"pinyin": "hé",
		"optionA": "and; with; harmony",
		"optionB": "to drink; interjection expressing surprise",
		"optionC": "Chinese language",
		"optionD": "good; well; nice; very; quite",
		"answer": "to drink; interjection expressing surprise"
	},

	{
		"question": "很",
		"pinyin": "hěn",
		"optionA": "and; with; harmony",
		"optionB": "to drink; interjection expressing surprise",
		"optionC": "very; rather; quite; (adverb of degree)",
		"optionD": "good; well; nice; very; quite",
		"answer": "very; rather; quite; (adverb of degree)"
	},

	{
		"question": "后面",
		"pinyin": "hòu mian",
		"optionA": "and; with; harmony",
		"optionB": "to drink; interjection expressing surprise",
		"optionC": "very; rather; quite; (adverb of degree)",
		"optionD": "rear; back; behind",
		"answer": "rear; back; behind"
	},

	{
		"question": "回",
		"pinyin": "huí",
		"optionA": "and; with; harmony",
		"optionB": "to return; to reply; to go back; (mw for matters or actions)",
		"optionC": "very; rather; quite; (adverb of degree)",
		"optionD": "rear; back; behind",
		"answer": "to return; to reply; to go back; (mw for matters or actions)"
	},

	{
		"question": "会",
		"pinyin": "huì",
		"optionA": "know how; be good at; be likely to",
		"optionB": "to return; to reply; to go back; (mw for matters or actions)",
		"optionC": "very; rather; quite; (adverb of degree)",
		"optionD": "rear; back; behind",
		"answer": "know how; be good at; be likely to"
	},

	{
		"question": "几",
		"pinyin": "jǐ",
		"optionA": "know how; be good at; be likely to",
		"optionB": "how many; several; a few | almost (Kangxi radical 16)",
		"optionC": "very; rather; quite; (adverb of degree)",
		"optionD": "rear; back; behind",
		"answer": "how many; several; a few | almost (Kangxi radical 16)"
	},

	{
		"question": "家",
		"pinyin": "jiā",
		"optionA": "know how; be good at; be likely to",
		"optionB": "how many; several; a few | almost (Kangxi radical 16)",
		"optionC": "very; rather; quite; (adverb of degree)",
		"optionD": "family; home; household",
		"answer": "family; home; household"
	},

	{
		"question": "叫",
		"pinyin": "jiào",
		"optionA": "know how; be good at; be likely to",
		"optionB": "to call; called; to yell",
		"optionC": "very; rather; quite; (adverb of degree)",
		"optionD": "family; home; household",
		"answer": "to call; called; to yell"
	},

	{
		"question": "今天",
		"pinyin": "jīn tiān",
		"optionA": "know how; be good at; be likely to",
		"optionB": "to call; called; to yell",
		"optionC": "today; at the present; now",
		"optionD": "family; home; household",
		"answer": "today; at the present; now"
	},

	{
		"question": "开",
		"pinyin": "kāi",
		"optionA": "nine",
		"optionB": "to open; to start; to turn on; to operate (a vehicle)",
		"optionC": "today; at the present; now",
		"optionD": "family; home; household",
		"answer": "to open; to start; to turn on; to operate (a vehicle)"
	},

	{
		"question": "看",
		"pinyin": "kàn",
		"optionA": "nine",
		"optionB": "to open; to start; to turn on; to operate (a vehicle)",
		"optionC": "see; look at; to watch; regard",
		"optionD": "family; home; household",
		"answer": "see; look at; to watch; regard"
	},

	{
		"question": "看见",
		"pinyin": "kàn jiàn",
		"optionA": "nine",
		"optionB": "to open; to start; to turn on; to operate (a vehicle)",
		"optionC": "see; catch sight of",
		"optionD": "family; home; household",
		"answer": "see; catch sight of"
	},

	{
		"question": "块",
		"pinyin": "kuài",
		"optionA": "lump; (mw: piece, chunk, sum of money)",
		"optionB": "to open; to start; to turn on; to operate (a vehicle)",
		"optionC": "see; catch sight of",
		"optionD": "family; home; household",
		"answer": "lump; (mw: piece, chunk, sum of money)"
	},

	{
		"question": "来",
		"pinyin": "lái",
		"optionA": "lump; (mw: piece, chunk, sum of money)",
		"optionB": "to open; to start; to turn on; to operate (a vehicle)",
		"optionC": "see; catch sight of",
		"optionD": "come; arrive; ever since; next",
		"answer": "come; arrive; ever since; next"
	},

	{
		"question": "老师",
		"pinyin": "lǎo shī",
		"optionA": "lump; (mw: piece, chunk, sum of money)",
		"optionB": "teacher",
		"optionC": "see; catch sight of",
		"optionD": "come; arrive; ever since; next",
		"answer": "teacher"
	},

	{
		"question": "了",
		"pinyin": "le",
		"optionA": "(particle for a new situation or completed action)",
		"optionB": "teacher",
		"optionC": "see; catch sight of",
		"optionD": "come; arrive; ever since; next",
		"answer": "(particle for a new situation or completed action)"
	},

	{
		"question": "冷",
		"pinyin": "lěng",
		"optionA": "(particle for a new situation or completed action)",
		"optionB": "teacher",
		"optionC": "cold",
		"optionD": "come; arrive; ever since; next",
		"answer": "cold"
	},

	{
		"question": "里",
		"pinyin": "lǐ",
		"optionA": "inside; internal; village, Chinese mile (~.5 km); neighborhood (Kangxi radical 166)",
		"optionB": "teacher",
		"optionC": "cold",
		"optionD": "come; arrive; ever since; next",
		"answer": "inside; internal; village, Chinese mile (~.5 km); neighborhood (Kangxi radical 166)"
	},

	{
		"question": "六",
		"pinyin": "liù",
		"optionA": "inside; internal; village, Chinese mile (~.5 km); neighborhood (Kangxi radical 166)",
		"optionB": "teacher",
		"optionC": "cold",
		"optionD": "six",
		"answer": "six"
	},

	{
		"question": "妈妈",
		"pinyin": "mā ma",
		"optionA": "mum; mama; mam; mother",
		"optionB": "teacher",
		"optionC": "cold",
		"optionD": "six",
		"answer": "mum; mama; mam; mother"
	},

	{
		"question": "吗",
		"pinyin": "ma",
		"optionA": "mum; mama; mam; mother",
		"optionB": "teacher",
		"optionC": "(question particle for yes/no questions)",
		"optionD": "six",
		"answer": "(question particle for yes/no questions)"
	},

	{
		"question": "买",
		"pinyin": "mǎi",
		"optionA": "mum; mama; mam; mother",
		"optionB": "to buy",
		"optionC": "(question particle for yes/no questions)",
		"optionD": "six",
		"answer": "to buy"
	},

	{
		"question": "猫",
		"pinyin": "māo",
		"optionA": "mum; mama; mam; mother",
		"optionB": "to buy",
		"optionC": "(question particle for yes/no questions)",
		"optionD": "cat",
		"answer": "cat"
	},

	{
		"question": "没关系",
		"pinyin": "méi guān xi",
		"optionA": "it doesn't matter; never mind",
		"optionB": "to buy",
		"optionC": "(question particle for yes/no questions)",
		"optionD": "cat",
		"answer": "it doesn't matter; never mind"
	},

	{
		"question": "没有",
		"pinyin": "méi yǒu",
		"optionA": "it doesn't matter; never mind",
		"optionB": "to buy",
		"optionC": "(question particle for yes/no questions)",
		"optionD": "not have; there is not; haven't; hasn't",
		"answer": "not have; there is not; haven't; hasn't"
	},

	{
		"question": "米饭",
		"pinyin": "mǐ fàn",
		"optionA": "it doesn't matter; never mind",
		"optionB": "(cooked) rice",
		"optionC": "(question particle for yes/no questions)",
		"optionD": "not have; there is not; haven't; hasn't",
		"answer": "(cooked) rice"
	},

	{
		"question": "名字",
		"pinyin": "míng zi",
		"optionA": "name",
		"optionB": "(cooked) rice",
		"optionC": "(question particle for yes/no questions)",
		"optionD": "not have; there is not; haven't; hasn't",
		"answer": "name"
	},

	{
		"question": "明天",
		"pinyin": "míng tiān",
		"optionA": "name",
		"optionB": "(cooked) rice",
		"optionC": "tomorrow",
		"optionD": "not have; there is not; haven't; hasn't",
		"answer": "tomorrow"
	},

	{
		"question": "哪",
		"pinyin": "nǎ",
		"optionA": "name",
		"optionB": "(cooked) rice",
		"optionC": "tomorrow",
		"optionD": "which; how",
		"answer": "which; how"
	},

	{
		"question": "哪儿",
		"pinyin": "nǎ r",
		"optionA": "name",
		"optionB": "where; wherever (Beijing accent)",
		"optionC": "tomorrow",
		"optionD": "which; how",
		"answer": "which; how"
	},

	{
		"question": "那",
		"pinyin": "nǎ",
		"optionA": "that; in that case; then",
		"optionB": "where; wherever (Beijing accent)",
		"optionC": "tomorrow",
		"optionD": "which; how",
		"answer": "that; in that case; then"
	},

	{
		"question": "呢",
		"pinyin": "ne",
		"optionA": "that; in that case; then",
		"optionB": "where; wherever (Beijing accent)",
		"optionC": "tomorrow",
		"optionD": "(modal particle ending a question); how about...?; what about...?",
		"answer": "(modal particle ending a question); how about...?; what about...?"
	},

	{
		"question": "能",
		"pinyin": "néng",
		"optionA": "that; in that case; then",
		"optionB": "where; wherever (Beijing accent)",
		"optionC": "tomorrow",
		"optionD": "can; be able; capable; energy; ability",
		"answer": "can; be able; capable; energy; ability"
	},

	{
		"question": "你",
		"pinyin": "nǐ",
		"optionA": "that; in that case; then",
		"optionB": "you (singular)",
		"optionC": "tomorrow",
		"optionD": "can; be able; capable; energy; ability",
		"answer": "you (singular)"
	},

	{
		"question": "年",
		"pinyin": "nián",
		"optionA": "that; in that case; then",
		"optionB": "you (singular)",
		"optionC": "year",
		"optionD": "can; be able; capable; energy; ability",
		"answer": "year"
	},

	{
		"question": "女儿",
		"pinyin": "nǚ ér",
		"optionA": "that; in that case; then",
		"optionB": "you (singular)",
		"optionC": "year",
		"optionD": "daughter",
		"answer": "daughter"
	},

	{
		"question": "朋友",
		"pinyin": "péng you",
		"optionA": "that; in that case; then",
		"optionB": "friend",
		"optionC": "year",
		"optionD": "daughter",
		"answer": "friend"
	},

	{
		"question": "漂亮",
		"pinyin": "piào liang",
		"optionA": "pretty; beautiful",
		"optionB": "friend",
		"optionC": "year",
		"optionD": "daughter",
		"answer": "pretty; beautiful"
	},

	{
		"question": "苹果",
		"pinyin": "píng guǒ",
		"optionA": "pretty; beautiful",
		"optionB": "friend",
		"optionC": "apple",
		"optionD": "daughter",
		"answer": "apple"
	},

	{
		"question": "七",
		"pinyin": "qī",
		"optionA": "pretty; beautiful",
		"optionB": "friend",
		"optionC": "apple",
		"optionD": "seven",
		"answer": "seven"
	},

	{
		"question": "前面",
		"pinyin": "qián miàn",
		"optionA": "in front; fore; at the head",
		"optionB": "friend",
		"optionC": "apple",
		"optionD": "seven",
		"answer": "in front; fore; at the head"
	},

	{
		"question": "钱",
		"pinyin": "qián",
		"optionA": "in front; fore; at the head",
		"optionB": "friend",
		"optionC": "money; coin",
		"optionD": "seven",
		"answer": "money; coin"
	},

	{
		"question": "请",
		"pinyin": "qǐng",
		"optionA": "in front; fore; at the head",
		"optionB": "please; invite; to request | treat",
		"optionC": "money; coin",
		"optionD": "seven",
		"answer": "please; invite; to request | treatn"
	},

	{
		"question": "去",
		"pinyin": "qù",
		"optionA": "in front; fore; at the head",
		"optionB": "please; invite; to request | treat",
		"optionC": "go; to leave",
		"optionD": "seven",
		"answer": "go; to leave"
	},

	{
		"question": "热",
		"pinyin": "rè",
		"optionA": "heat; hot; heat up",
		"optionB": "please; invite; to request | treat",
		"optionC": "go; to leave",
		"optionD": "seven",
		"answer": "heat; hot; heat up"
	},

	{
		"question": "人",
		"pinyin": "rén",
		"optionA": "heat; hot; heat up",
		"optionB": "person; man; people (Kangxi radical 9)",
		"optionC": "go; to leave",
		"optionD": "seven",
		"answer": "person; man; people (Kangxi radical 9)"
	},

	{
		"question": "认识",
		"pinyin": "rèn shi",
		"optionA": "heat; hot; heat up",
		"optionB": "person; man; people (Kangxi radical 9)",
		"optionC": "go; to leave",
		"optionD": "know; recognize; acquainted with (a person)",
		"answer": "know; recognize; acquainted with (a person)"
	},

	{
		"question": "三",
		"pinyin": "sān",
		"optionA": "three",
		"optionB": "person; man; people (Kangxi radical 9)",
		"optionC": "go; to leave",
		"optionD": "know; recognize; acquainted with (a person)",
		"answer": "three"
	},

	{
		"question": "商店",
		"pinyin": "shāng diàn",
		"optionA": "three",
		"optionB": "shop，store",
		"optionC": "go; to leave",
		"optionD": "know; recognize; acquainted with (a person)",
		"answer": "shop，store"
	},

	{
		"question": "上",
		"pinyin": "shàng",
		"optionA": "three",
		"optionB": "shop，store",
		"optionC": "above; up; on top; get on; go up",
		"optionD": "know; recognize; acquainted with (a person)",
		"answer": "above; up; on top; get on; go up"
	},

	{
		"question": "上午",
		"pinyin": "shàng wǔ",
		"optionA": "three",
		"optionB": "shop，store",
		"optionC": "above; up; on top; get on; go up",
		"optionD": "late morning (before noon)",
		"answer": "late morning (before noon)"
	},

	{
		"question": "少",
		"pinyin": "shǎo",
		"optionA": "few; little; lack; lose",
		"optionB": "shop，store",
		"optionC": "above; up; on top; get on; go up",
		"optionD": "late morning (before noon)",
		"answer": "few; little; lack; lose"
	},

	{
		"question": "谁",
		"pinyin": "shéi",
		"optionA": "few; little; lack; lose",
		"optionB": "who",
		"optionC": "above; up; on top; get on; go up",
		"optionD": "late morning (before noon)",
		"answer": "who"
	},

	{
		"question": "什么",
		"pinyin": "shén me",
		"optionA": "few; little; lack; lose",
		"optionB": "who",
		"optionC": "what; whatever; something",
		"optionD": "late morning (before noon)",
		"answer": "what; whatever; something"
	},

	{
		"question": "十",
		"pinyin": "shí",
		"optionA": "ten (Kangxi radical 24)",
		"optionB": "who",
		"optionC": "what; whatever; something",
		"optionD": "late morning (before noon)",
		"answer": "ten (Kangxi radical 24)"
	},

	{
		"question": "时候",
		"pinyin": "shí hou",
		"optionA": "ten (Kangxi radical 24)",
		"optionB": "who",
		"optionC": "what; whatever; something",
		"optionD": "time; length of time; moment",
		"answer": "time; length of time; moment"
	},

	{
		"question": "是",
		"pinyin": "shì",
		"optionA": "ten (Kangxi radical 24)",
		"optionB": "be; is; are; am",
		"optionC": "what; whatever; something",
		"optionD": "time; length of time; moment",
		"answer": "be; is; are; am"
	},

	{
		"question": "书",
		"pinyin": "shū",
		"optionA": "book; letter",
		"optionB": "be; is; are; am",
		"optionC": "what; whatever; something",
		"optionD": "time; length of time; moment",
		"answer": "book; letter"
	},

	{
		"question": "水",
		"pinyin": "shuǐ",
		"optionA": "book; letter",
		"optionB": "be; is; are; am",
		"optionC": "water (Kangxi radical 85)",
		"optionD": "time; length of time; moment",
		"answer": "water (Kangxi radical 85)"
	},

	{
		"question": "水果",
		"pinyin": "shuǐ guǒ",
		"optionA": "book; letter",
		"optionB": "be; is; are; am",
		"optionC": "water (Kangxi radical 85)",
		"optionD": "fruit",
		"answer": "fruit"
	},

	{
		"question": "睡觉",
		"pinyin": "shuì jiào",
		"optionA": "book; letter",
		"optionB": "be; is; are; am",
		"optionC": "to sleep; go to bed",
		"optionD": "fruit",
		"answer": "to sleep; go to bed"
	},

	{
		"question": "说",
		"pinyin": "shuō",
		"optionA": "book; letter",
		"optionB": "speak; to say; to talk",
		"optionC": "to sleep; go to bed",
		"optionD": "fruit",
		"answer": "speak; to say; to talk"
	},

	{
		"question": "四",
		"pinyin": "sì",
		"optionA": "four",
		"optionB": "speak; to say; to talk",
		"optionC": "to sleep; go to bed",
		"optionD": "fruit",
		"answer": "four"
	},

	{
		"question": "岁",
		"pinyin": "suì",
		"optionA": "four",
		"optionB": "speak; to say; to talk",
		"optionC": "to sleep; go to bed",
		"optionD": "years old",
		"answer": "years old"
	},

	{
		"question": "他",
		"pinyin": "tā",
		"optionA": "four",
		"optionB": "speak; to say; to talk",
		"optionC": "he; him",
		"optionD": "years old",
		"answer": "he; him"
	},

	{
		"question": "她",
		"pinyin": "tā",
		"optionA": "four",
		"optionB": "she; her",
		"optionC": "he; him",
		"optionD": "years old",
		"answer": "she; her"
	},

	{
		"question": "太",
		"pinyin": "tài",
		"optionA": "too (much); excessively; highest; greatest",
		"optionB": "she; her",
		"optionC": "he; him",
		"optionD": "years old",
		"answer": "too (much); excessively; highest; greatest"
	},

	{
		"question": "天气",
		"pinyin": "tiān qì",
		"optionA": "too (much); excessively; highest; greatest",
		"optionB": "she; her",
		"optionC": "he; him",
		"optionD": "weather",
		"answer": "weather"
	},

	{
		"question": "听",
		"pinyin": "tīng",
		"optionA": "too (much); excessively; highest; greatest",
		"optionB": "she; her",
		"optionC": "listen; hear; heed",
		"optionD": "weather",
		"answer": "listen; hear; heed"
	},

	{
		"question": "同学",
		"pinyin": "tóng xué",
		"optionA": "too (much); excessively; highest; greatest",
		"optionB": "fellow student; schoolmate",
		"optionC": "listen; hear; heed",
		"optionD": "weather",
		"answer": "fellow student; schoolmate"
	},

	{
		"question": "喂",
		"pinyin": "wéi",
		"optionA": "too (much); excessively; highest; greatest",
		"optionB": "fellow student; schoolmate",
		"optionC": "listen; hear; heed",
		"optionD": "hey; hello (on the phone)",
		"answer": "hey; hello (on the phone)"
	},

	{
		"question": "我",
		"pinyin": "wǒ",
		"optionA": "I; me",
		"optionB": "fellow student; schoolmate",
		"optionC": "listen; hear; heed",
		"optionD": "hey; hello (on the phone)",
		"answer": "I; me"
	},

	{
		"question": "我们",
		"pinyin": "wǒ men",
		"optionA": "I; me",
		"optionB": "fellow student; schoolmate",
		"optionC": "we; us",
		"optionD": "hey; hello (on the phone)",
		"answer": "we; us"
	},

	{
		"question": "五",
		"pinyin": "wǔ",
		"optionA": "I; me",
		"optionB": "five",
		"optionC": "we; us",
		"optionD": "hey; hello (on the phone)",
		"answer": "five"
	},

	{
		"question": "喜欢",
		"pinyin": "xǐ huan",
		"optionA": "I; me",
		"optionB": "five",
		"optionC": "we; us",
		"optionD": "to like; be fond of",
		"answer": "to like; be fond of"
	},

	{
		"question": "下",
		"pinyin": "xià",
		"optionA": "I; me",
		"optionB": "five",
		"optionC": "descend; fall; below; down; next; the second (of two parts)",
		"optionD": "to like; be fond of",
		"answer": "descend; fall; below; down; next; the second (of two parts)"
	},

	{
		"question": "下午",
		"pinyin": "xià wǔ",
		"optionA": "I; me",
		"optionB": "afternoon",
		"optionC": "descend; fall; below; down; next; the second (of two parts)",
		"optionD": "to like; be fond of",
		"answer": "afternoon"
	},

	{
		"question": "下雨",
		"pinyin": "xià yǔ",
		"optionA": "I; me",
		"optionB": "afternoon",
		"optionC": "to rain",
		"optionD": "to like; be fond of",
		"answer": "to rain"
	},

	{
		"question": "先生",
		"pinyin": "xiān sheng",
		"optionA": "I; me",
		"optionB": "afternoon",
		"optionC": "to rain",
		"optionD": "Mr.; Sir",
		"answer": "Mr.; Sir"
	},

	{
		"question": "现在",
		"pinyin": "xiàn zài",
		"optionA": "now",
		"optionB": "afternoon",
		"optionC": "to rain",
		"optionD": "Mr.; Sir",
		"answer": "now"
	},

	{
		"question": "想",
		"pinyin": "xiǎng",
		"optionA": "now",
		"optionB": "think; believe; suppose; would like to; remember with longing; to miss",
		"optionC": "to rain",
		"optionD": "Mr.; Sir",
		"answer": "think; believe; suppose; would like to; remember with longing; to miss"
	},

	{
		"question": "小",
		"pinyin": "xiǎo",
		"optionA": "now",
		"optionB": "think; believe; suppose; would like to; remember with longing; to miss",
		"optionC": "to rain",
		"optionD": "small; young (Kangxi radical 42)",
		"answer": "small; young (Kangxi radical 42)"
	},

	{
		"question": "小姐",
		"pinyin": "xiǎo jie",
		"optionA": "now",
		"optionB": "young lady; miss; Ms.",
		"optionC": "to rain",
		"optionD": "small; young (Kangxi radical 42)",
		"answer": "young lady; miss; Ms."
	},

	{
		"question": "些",
		"pinyin": "xiē",
		"optionA": "some; few; several; (mw for indefinite amount)",
		"optionB": "young lady; miss; Ms.",
		"optionC": "to rain",
		"optionD": "small; young (Kangxi radical 42)",
		"answer": "some; few; several; (mw for indefinite amount)"
	},

	{
		"question": "写",
		"pinyin": "xiě",
		"optionA": "some; few; several; (mw for indefinite amount)",
		"optionB": "young lady; miss; Ms.",
		"optionC": "to write; to compose",
		"optionD": "small; young (Kangxi radical 42)",
		"answer": "to write; to compose"
	},

	{
		"question": "谢谢",
		"pinyin": "xiè xie",
		"optionA": "to thank; thank you",
		"optionB": "young lady; miss; Ms.",
		"optionC": "to write; to compose",
		"optionD": "small; young (Kangxi radical 42)",
		"answer": "to thank; thank you"
	},

	{
		"question": "星期",
		"pinyin": "xīng qī",
		"optionA": "to thank; thank you",
		"optionB": "young lady; miss; Ms.",
		"optionC": "to write; to compose",
		"optionD": "week",
		"answer": "week"
	},

	{
		"question": "学生",
		"pinyin": "xué sheng",
		"optionA": "student",
		"optionB": "young lady; miss; Ms.",
		"optionC": "to write; to compose",
		"optionD": "week",
		"answer": "student"
	},

	{
		"question": "学习",
		"pinyin": "xué xí",
		"optionA": "student",
		"optionB": "learn; to study; emulate",
		"optionC": "to write; to compose",
		"optionD": "week",
		"answer": "learn; to study; emulate"
	},

	{
		"question": "学校",
		"pinyin": "xué xiào",
		"optionA": "student",
		"optionB": "learn; to study; emulate",
		"optionC": "to write; to compose",
		"optionD": "school",
		"answer": "school"
	},

	{
		"question": "一",
		"pinyin": "yī",
		"optionA": "student",
		"optionB": "learn; to study; emulate",
		"optionC": "one; once; a (article) (Kangxi radical 1)",
		"optionD": "school",
		"answer": "one; once; a (article) (Kangxi radical 1)"
	},

	{
		"question": "一点儿",
		"pinyin": "yī diǎn r",
		"optionA": "a bit; a few; a little; Beijing accent",
		"optionB": "learn; to study; emulate",
		"optionC": "one; once; a (article) (Kangxi radical 1)",
		"optionD": "school",
		"answer": "a bit; a few; a little; Beijing accent"
	},

	{
		"question": "衣服",
		"pinyin": "yī fu",
		"optionA": "a bit; a few; a little; Beijing accent",
		"optionB": "learn; to study; emulate",
		"optionC": "clothes",
		"optionD": "school",
		"answer": "clothes"
	},

	{
		"question": "医生",
		"pinyin": "yī shēng",
		"optionA": "doctor",
		"optionB": "learn; to study; emulate",
		"optionC": "clothes",
		"optionD": "school",
		"answer": "doctor"
	},

	{
		"question": "医院",
		"pinyin": "yī yuàn",
		"optionA": "doctor",
		"optionB": "learn; to study; emulate",
		"optionC": "clothes",
		"optionD": "hospital",
		"answer": "hospital"
	},

	{
		"question": "椅子",
		"pinyin": "yǐ zi",
		"optionA": "doctor",
		"optionB": "chair",
		"optionC": "clothes",
		"optionD": "hospital",
		"answer": "chair"
	},

	{
		"question": "有",
		"pinyin": "yǒu",
		"optionA": "doctor",
		"optionB": "chair",
		"optionC": "have; there is",
		"optionD": "hospital",
		"answer": "have; there is"
	},

	{
		"question": "月",
		"pinyin": "yuè",
		"optionA": "moon; month (Kangxi radical 74: moon | (Kangxi radical 130: flesh)",
		"optionB": "chair",
		"optionC": "have; there is",
		"optionD": "hospital",
		"answer": "moon; month (Kangxi radical 74: moon | (Kangxi radical 130: flesh)"
	},

	{
		"question": "再见",
		"pinyin": "zài jiàn",
		"optionA": "moon; month (Kangxi radical 74: moon | (Kangxi radical 130: flesh)",
		"optionB": "chair",
		"optionC": "have; there is",
		"optionD": "goodbye; see you later",
		"answer": "goodbye; see you later"
	},

	{
		"question": "在",
		"pinyin": "zài",
		"optionA": "at; on; in; exist; (indicating an action in progress)",
		"optionB": "chair",
		"optionC": "have; there is",
		"optionD": "goodbye; see you later",
		"answer": "at; on; in; exist; (indicating an action in progress)"
	},

	{
		"question": "怎么",
		"pinyin": "zěn me",
		"optionA": "at; on; in; exist; (indicating an action in progress)",
		"optionB": "how",
		"optionC": "have; there is",
		"optionD": "goodbye; see you later",
		"answer": "how"
	},

	{
		"question": "怎么样",
		"pinyin": "zěn me yàng",
		"optionA": "how about; how is/was it",
		"optionB": "how",
		"optionC": "have; there is",
		"optionD": "goodbye; see you later",
		"answer": "how about; how is/was it"
	},

	{
		"question": "这",
		"pinyin": "zhè",
		"optionA": "how about; how is/was it",
		"optionB": "how",
		"optionC": "have; there is",
		"optionD": "this; these",
		"answer": "this; these"
	},

	{
		"question": "中国",
		"pinyin": "Zhōng guó",
		"optionA": "how about; how is/was it",
		"optionB": "how",
		"optionC": "China",
		"optionD": "this; these",
		"answer": "China"
	},

	{
		"question": "中午",
		"pinyin": "zhōng wǔ",
		"optionA": "how about; how is/was it",
		"optionB": "noon; midday",
		"optionC": "China",
		"optionD": "this; these",
		"answer": "noon; midday"
	},

	{
		"question": "住",
		"pinyin": "zhù",
		"optionA": "how about; how is/was it",
		"optionB": "noon; midday",
		"optionC": "China",
		"optionD": "to live; reside; to stop",
		"answer": "to live; reside; to stop"
	},

	{
		"question": "桌子",
		"pinyin": "zhuō zi",
		"optionA": "how about; how is/was it",
		"optionB": "noon; midday",
		"optionC": "table; desk",
		"optionD": "to live; reside; to stop",
		"answer": "table; desk"
	},

	{
		"question": "字",
		"pinyin": "zì",
		"optionA": "word; letter; character",
		"optionB": "noon; midday",
		"optionC": "table; desk",
		"optionD": "to live; reside; to stop",
		"answer": "word; letter; character"
	},

	{
		"question": "昨天",
		"pinyin": "zuó tiān",
		"optionA": "word; letter; character",
		"optionB": "yesterday",
		"optionC": "table; desk",
		"optionD": "to live; reside; to stop",
		"answer": "yesterday"
	},

	{
		"question": "坐",
		"pinyin": "zuò",
		"optionA": "word; letter; character",
		"optionB": "yesterday",
		"optionC": "sit; take a seat",
		"optionD": "to live; reside; to stop",
		"answer": "sit; take a seat"
	},

	{
		"question": "做",
		"pinyin": "zuò",
		"optionA": "do; make; to produce; be; to cook; write",
		"optionB": "yesterday",
		"optionC": "sit; take a seat",
		"optionD": "to live; reside; to stop",
		"answer": "do; make; to produce; be; to cook; write"
	}
]
